A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  - 1926.
    - Massaponax, 1926 (Box 165)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1926 (Box 165)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, 1926 (Box 165)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk (2 folders), 1926 (Box 165)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1926 (Box 165)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Norton and Northern, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1926 (Box 166)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Roanoke, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Roaring Fork, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Sandston, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company (2 folders), 1926 (Box 167)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1926 (Box 167)
    - Southern, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Tazewell Street, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Valley, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Virginia Central (2 folders), 1926 (Box 168)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, Railway Department, 1926 (Box 168)
    - Virginian, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Virginia Southern, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1926 (Box 169)
    - Winchester and Western, 1926 (Box 169)
  - 1927.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1927 (Box 169)
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1927 (Box 170)
    - Clinchfield, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Danville and Western, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Interstate, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Lake Drummond Canal and Water Company, 1927 (Box 171)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Massaponax, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Mt. Vernon, Alexandria, and Washington, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1927 (Box 172)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1927 (Box 172)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Norton and Northern, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1927 (Box 173)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Roaring Fork, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Sandston Railway, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Southern Railway, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Tazewell Street, 1927 (Box 174)
    - Valley, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginia Central, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginian, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginian Public Service, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Virginia Southern, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1927 (Box 175)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1927 (Box 176)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1927 (Box 176)
    - Winchester and Western, 1927 (Box 176)
  - 1928.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1928 (Box 176)
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1928 (Box 176)
    - Atlanticc and Danville, 1928 (Box 176)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1928 (Box 176)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1928 (Box 176)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio 1928 (Box 177)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Clinchfield, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Danville and Western, 1928 (Box 177)
    - Danville Traction and Power, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Interstate, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Massaponax, 1928 (Box 178)
    - Mt. Vernon, Alexandria, and Washington, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1928 (Box 179)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Norton and Northern, 1928 (Box 179)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Roaring Fork, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1928 (Box 180)
    - Sandston, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Southern, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Tazewell Street, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Valley, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1928 (Box 181)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Virginia Central, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Virginian, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Virginia Southern, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1928 (Box 182)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1928 (Box 183)
    - Winchester and Western, 1928 (Box 183)
  - 1929.
    - American Railway Express Company, 1929 (Box 183)
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1929 (Box 183)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1929 (Box 183)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1929 (Box 183)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1929 (Box 183)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1929 (Box 183)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Clinchfield, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Danville and Western, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1929 (Box 184)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Interstate, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Lynchburg, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1929 (Box 185)
    - Massaponax, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Mt. Vernon, Alexandria, and Washington, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1929 (Box 186)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1929 (Box 186)
    - Norton and Northern, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1929 (Box 187)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Roaring Fork, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Sandston, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Southeastern, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1929 (Box 188)
    - Tazewell Street, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Valley, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginia Central, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company (2 folders), 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginian, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1929 (Box 189)
    - Virginia Public Service Company, 1929 (Box 190)
    - Virginia Southern, 1929 (Box 190)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1929 (Box 190)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1929 (Box 190)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1929 (Box 190)
    - Winchester and Western, 1929 (Box 190)
  - 1930.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1930 (Box 190)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1930 (Box 190)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Caroline, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Clichfield, 1930 (Box 191)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Danville and Western, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Interstate, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Mt. Vernon, Alexandria, and Washington, 1930 (Box 192)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1930 (Box 193)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Norton and Northern, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1930 (Box 193)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Sandston, 1930 (Box 194)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Southern, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Tazewell Street, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Valley 1930 (Box 195)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Virginia Central, 1930 (Box 195)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Virginian, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Virginia Public Service, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Virginia Southern, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Winchester and Wardenville, 1930 (Box 196)
    - Winchester and Western, 1930 (Box 196)
  - 1931.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1931 (Box 197)
    - Clinchfield, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Danville and Western, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Delaware, Maryland and Virginia, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Interstate, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1931 (Box 198)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Mt. Vernon, Alexandria, and Washington, 1931 (Box 199)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1931 (Box 199)
    - Norton and Northern, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1931 (Box 200)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Sandston, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Shenandoah Traction Company, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Southeastern Express Company, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Southern, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Valley, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1931 (Box 201)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Virginia Central, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Virginian, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Virginian Public Service, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Virginia Southern, 1931 (Box 202)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1931 (Box 202A)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1931 (Box 202A)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1931 (Box 202A)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1931 (Box 202A)
  - 1932.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1932 (Box 202A)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1932 (Box 202A)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1932 (Box 203)
    - Clinchfield, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Danville and Western, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Interstate, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1932 (Box 204)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1932 (Box 205)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1932 (Box 205)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1932 (Box 205)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1932 (Box 205)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1932 (Box 205)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1932 (Box 205)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1932 (Box 205)
    - Princeton Power Company 1932 (Box 205)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1932 (Box 206)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Roaring Fork, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Sandston, 1932 (Box 206)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Southeastern Express Company (2 folders), 1932 (Box 207)
    - Southern, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Tazewell Street, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Valley, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Virginia Central, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1932 (Box 207)
    - Virginian, 1932 (Box 208)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1932 (Box 208)
    - Virginia Public Service, 1932 (Box 208)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1932 (Box 208)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1932 (Box 208)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1932 (Box 208)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1932 (Box 208)
  - 1933.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1933 (Box 208)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1933 (Box 208)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1933 (Box 208)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Clinchfield, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Danville and Western, 1933 (Box 209)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Interstate, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Lynchburg Light and Traction Company, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1933 (Box 210)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1933 (Box 210)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1933 (Box 211)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1933 (Box 211)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1933 (Box 211)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1933 (Box 211)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1933 (Box 211)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1933 (Box 211)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1933 (Box 211)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg (2 folders), 1933 (Box 212)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1933 (Box 212)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1933 (Box 212)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1933 (Box 212)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1933 (Box 212)
    - Southwestern Express Company (2 folders), 1933 (Box 212)
    - Southern, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Valley, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginia Central, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginian, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1933 (Box 213)
    - Virginia Public Service Company (2 folders), 1933 (Box 213)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1933 (Box 214)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1933 (Box 214)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1933 (Box 214)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1933 (Box 214)
  - 1934.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1934 (Box 214)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1934 (Box 214)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1934 (Box 214)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1934 (Box 214)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1934 (Box 214)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Clinchfield, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Danville and Western, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1934 (Box 215)
    - Franklin and Carolina, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Interstate, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1934 (Box 216)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1934 (Box 216)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1934 (Box 217)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Richmond - Ashland, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Richmond - Fairfield, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1934 (Box 217)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Rosslyn Connectin, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Southeastern Express Company (2 folders), 1934 (Box 218)
    - Southern, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Valley, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1934 (Box 218)
    - Virginia Central, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Virginian, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Virginia Public Service, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1934 (Box 219)
    - Winchester and Wardensville, 1934 (Box 219)
  - 1935.
    - Arlington and Fairfax, 1935 (Box 219)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1935 (Box 219)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Clinchfield, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1935 (Box 220)
    - Danville and Western, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Interstate, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1935 (Box 221)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1935 (Box 221)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1935 (Box 222)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1935 (Box 222)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1935 (Box 222)
    - Petersburg - Hopewell and City Point, 1935 (Box 222)
    - Princeton Power Company, 1935 (Box 222)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1935 (Box 222)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1935 (Box 223)